jobs2shop.com 2019-02-16

# Jobs2Shop | Privacy

#### _**What information do we collect?**_

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or Age, Gender, Zip. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

#### _**What do we use your information for?**_

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, promotions, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

We may use and/or share the information that we collect and/or obtain in any manner in our sole discretion. Also, we use individual information to provide promotional offers to you. The promotional offers may be made to you by us and/or unrelated and/or unaffiliated third parties by means of email advertising, telephone marketing, postal mail, and/or by any other means of communication. By registering at this Website, or other third party web sites as described herein, you agree that such act constitutes and inquiry and/or application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (16 CFR Section 310 et seq.), as amended from time to time (“ATSR”). Notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission’s Do-Not-Call List, we reserved the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with ATSR. 

#### _**How do we protect your information?**_

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit a request or access your personal information.

These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information, SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely or PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

#### _**Do we use cookies?**_

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

Your computer permits you to change the settings on your web browser to not accept and/or disable Cookies and Recording Tools. However, if you do not accept Cookies and Recording Tools used by Jobs2shop and our Advertisers, you may not be able to use certain functions on certain websites. More importantly, if you do not accept Cookies and Recording Tools you will not receive credit for offers or other actions completed by you because we and our Advertisers are unable to track and record your activity. If you do not want to accept Cookies and Recording Tools, you must stop using this website.

#### _**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**_

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### _**Third party links**_

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. Jobs2shop is in no way responsible for the privacy practices employed by other sites. Such websites may independently collect data, solicit personal information, or send their own cookies to your computer. We are not responsible for any use of the information, including click-stream data, and you may create and disclose when visiting such third party sites.We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.

#### _**Social Media Features**_

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

#### _**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**_

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

#### _**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**_

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

#### _**CAN-SPAM Compliance**_

We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.

#### _**Online Privacy Policy Only**_

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

#### _**Your Consent**_

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

#### _**Changes to our Privacy Policy**_

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on February 28, 2012

#### _**Contacting Us**_

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.  
www.jobs2shop.com  
PO Box 1543  
Port Washington, NY 11050 USA  
support(at)obs2shop.com

#### _**Privacy Policy Customer Pledge**_

We pledge to you, our customer, that we have made a dedicated effort to bring our privacy policy in line with the following important privacy laws and initiatives:  
Federal Trade Commission Fair  
California Online Privacy Protection Act  
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act  
Privacy Alliance  
Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act 

If at any time you have a cause that needs to be disputed please fill out the Trust Guard Dispute Resolution form.

Respectfully,

Director  
www.jobs2shop.com.
